<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maintenance Service on quaether</title>
    <link>https://quaether.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Maintenance Service on quaether</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://quaether.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Taking the technology to the next level</title>
      <link>https://quaether.com/blog/posts/6-29-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quaether.com/blog/posts/6-29-21/</guid>
      <description>For many first-time visitors to the site, the concepts behind BSQ technology can be novel and even generate some skepticism. However, BSQ Neo devices have been on the market for years, and were tested by numerous customers who saw favorable changes in their lives thanks to the incorporation of technology.
The BSQ technology was created by Carlos Belohlavek, a visionary man for some and a teacher for the few who had the opportunity to follow his teachings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming the pandemic with BSQ</title>
      <link>https://quaether.com/blog/posts/6-30-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quaether.com/blog/posts/6-30-21/</guid>
      <description>For many people, the beginning of the decade meant a change in their work routine, a distancing from their friends and the emergence of negative emotions, such as anxiety or uncertainty. Although there are different reactions to the same event, they all share the following results: a weakened biofield and a feeling of exhaustion, produced by external influences.
While BSQ technology does not replace the recommendations of physicians or other qualified personnel, strengthening the biofield can open a window for those who are coping with illness, or have suffered emotional losses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a code from scratch</title>
      <link>https://quaether.com/blog/posts/6-31-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quaether.com/blog/posts/6-31-21/</guid>
      <description>Before starting the formal explanation, it is necessary to remember that the codes, although they are NOT essential for the operation of the BSQ technology, the practice of this mental exercise allows the user to tune their biofield with the BSQ signal and improve the results obtained.
The first necessary component, prior to incorporating the concepts of the card, is the final objective of the code. The same chain of concepts can generate different codes as it is oriented to different objectives.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
